Buh! Buh! Buh! Buh! Buh! Buh!
Walking down the strip in 83
Me on lights are flickering just for me
Ock it sounds and synthesize a play
California dream in every single day
Boombox is blast, we're holding sway
Serves up handbags, motorbikes
We're living loud and proud today
Costco G-Shop, Jeremy Payne
These are the things that drop me insane
Costco G-Shop, live in the dream
Jeremy Payne, that's my theme song it seems
Sunset, boulevard, a quarter past eight
Roller and Keros don't hesitate
Cassette tape spinning in the car
Traveling near and throwing it far
Boombox is blast, we're holding sway
Serves up handbags, motorbikes
We're living loud and proud today
Costco G-Shop, Jeremy Payne
These are the things that drop me insane
Costco G-Shop, live in the dream
Jeremy Payne, that's my theme song it seems
83, it's calling me
Back to where we used to be
Every beat, every tone, this is how we make it home
Costco G-Shop, Jeremy Payne
These are the things that drop me insane
Costco G-Shop, live in the dream
Jeremy Payne, that's my theme song it seems
This is how we make it home